welcome to the credential premium
payment platform this is an online
platform that allows you to make your
premium payments
online follow these Easy Steps step one
you as our client will receive a message
from credential in the message you
should also see a link to help set up
your payment details for credential
Zambia iPhone users may receive a
timeout error message when making
payments to prevent this go to settings
on your iPhone and search Safari then
under privacy and security for Safari
switch of the option prevent cross- site
tracking and go back to the link in the
text message for Android users you be
good to go without any issues step two
follow the link which will lead you to
ww. Reay collect.com once you're on the
landing page please verify that your
personal information policy number and
monthly installment amount is correct
and click next after being directed to
this billing page ensure that you enter
the correct details that is the correct
card number the expiring date of the
card the card holder name and the
security code once you enter these
details then you will click next which
will open the review page for you to
review all the details and once verified
proceed to pay once you click pay now
the payment will go through please note
that the one quaa is only a tokenization
fee as each link that the client
receives will be uniquely associated
with a specific
policy should you have any challenges
feel free to reach our customer
experience number 752 or email info@
prudential.com
credential helping you get the most out
of
life